Better to suffer injustice than to commit it.
A Hidden Life is a history, drama, war film directed by Terrence Malick.
Austrian farmer Franz Jägerstätter faces the threat of execution for
refusing to fight for the Nazis during World War II.
Franz Jägerstätter, played by August Diehl.
Fani Jägerstätter, played by Valerie Pachner.
Resie, played by Maria Simon.
Rosalia Jägerstätter, played by Karin Neuhäuser.
Fr Ferdinand Fürthauer, played by Tobias Moretti.
Lorenz Schwaninger, played by Ulrich Matthes.
A Hidden Life is a 2019 epic historical drama film
written and directed by Terrence Malick.
It stars August Diehl, Valerie Pachner, and Matthias Schoenaerts, with
Michael Nyqvist and Bruno Ganz in their final performances.
The film depicts the life of Franz Jägerstätter, an Austrian farmer and devout
Catholic who refused to fight for the Nazis in World War II.
The title is taken from George Eliot's Middlemarch:...
for the growing good of the world is partly dependent on unhistoric acts; and that things are not so ill with you and me as they
might have been, is half owing to the number who lived faithfully a hidden life, and rest in unvisited tombs.
The film premiered at the 2019 Cannes Film Festival on May 19, and was
theatrically released in the United States on December 13.
It received critical acclaim upon release.
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship,
nazi, world war ii, austria, biography.
The tone is dark and emotional.